<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Jon's Garden Notes on Fammatre</title><link>https://www.fammatre.org/jons-garden-notes/</link><description>Recent content in Jon's Garden Notes on Fammatre</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://www.fammatre.org/jons-garden-notes/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Garden Brainstorming</title><link>https://www.fammatre.org/jons-garden-notes/brainstorming/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.fammatre.org/jons-garden-notes/brainstorming/</guid><description>This page is just for brainstorming ideas for Fammatre&amp;rsquo;s garden program.
Communication # Shared &amp;ldquo;todo&amp;rdquo; list. Website with notes and ideas. Maintenance # Replace any rotting wood.
Add screws for loose boards.
Sand and paint
Create an irrigation system map/plan.
Repair irrigation system.
Remove or repair broken tools and unneeded debris.
Create an inventory of our equipment and supplies.
Determine what equipment and supplies are needed.
Create a map of our garden beds with descriptions of what is currently planted.</description></item><item><title>What can we plant?</title><link>https://www.fammatre.org/jons-garden-notes/planting-by-month/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.fammatre.org/jons-garden-notes/planting-by-month/</guid><description>This page is a schedule of what can be planted for each month based on Fammatre&amp;rsquo;s USDA plant hardiness zone (9b).
Planting by month # July # Brussel sprout (transplant) Chayote (plant fruit) Okra (transplant) Summer squash (transplant or direct seed) Zucchini (transplant or direct seed) August # Arugula (direct seed) Beet (direct seed) Broccoli (transplant) Brussel sprouts (transplant) Cabbage (transplant) Napa Cabbage (transplant or direct seed) Chayote (plant fruit) Cilantro (direct seed) Fava bean (direct seed) Leek (transplant) Pea (direct seed) September # Artichoke (transplant) Arugula (transplant or direct seed) Beet (transplant or direct seed) Bok Choy (transplant or direct seed) Broccoli (transplant) Cabbage (transplant) Napa Cabbage (transplant or direct seed) Carrots (direct seed) Cauliflower (transplant) Chard (transplant or direct seed) Chaoyte (plant fruit) Parsnip (direct seed) Pea (transplant or direct seed) Radish (direct seed) Spinach (transplant or direct seed) Turnip (transplant or direct seed) October # Artichoke (transplant) Arugula November # Onion (transplant)</description></item></channel></rss>